A Guide to the Records of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1996-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series IX. Restoration of Rights Files, 1996-2006 (accessions 42418 and 42513) RESTRICTED FOR 75 YEARS., Extent: 47.60 cu. ft. (Box 138-274)
  - Subseries B: Governor Mark R. Warner, 2002-2006.
    - 15 January 2005 to 14 January 2006 (Accession 42513)
      - McCants, Shirley, granted 1 November 2005 (Box 252, Folder 1)
      - McCart, David Bruce, granted 12 April 2005 (Box 252, Folder 1)
      - McCarthy, Helen, granted 28 November 2005 (Box 252, Folder 1)
      - McCauley, Robert Ernest, Sr., granted 25 July 2005 (Box 252, Folder 1)
      - McCloud, Errol Rodney, granted 14 September 2005 (Box 252, Folder 1)
      - McClure, Paul Michael, granted 1 August 2005 (Box 252, Folder 1)
      - McCormack, David J., granted 25 July 2005 (Box 252, Folder 2)
      - McCown, Verenda Ann, granted 26 August 2005 (Box 252, Folder 2)
      - McCray, Babet D., granted 4 January 2006 (Box 252, Folder 2)
      - McCray, Toni G., granted 20 June 2005 (Box 252, Folder 2)
      - McDearmon, Kathy S., granted 23 February 2005 (Box 252, Folder 2)
      - McDonald, Leslie L., granted 1 November 2005 (Box 252, Folder 2)
      - McDowell, Thomas Kent, Jr., granted 1 July 2005 (Box 252, Folder 2)
      - McFarland, Paul W., granted 25 July 2005 (Box 252, Folder 3)
      - McGhee, Michelle Lynne, granted 31 August 2005 (Box 252, Folder 3)
      - McGhee, Patricia Mae, granted 17 June 2005 (Box 252, Folder 3)
      - McKinney, Troy Clay, granted 15 February 2005 (Box 252, Folder 3)
      - McLain, Jamie D., granted 26 August 2005 (Box 252, Folder 3)
      - McNair, Crystal Ann, granted 19 August 2005 (Box 252, Folder 3)
      - McNeill, Gaston, Jr., granted 4 January 2006 (Box 252, Folder 3)
      - McNeill, Pamela Colleen, granted 24 January 2005 (Box 252, Folder 4)
      - McPeak, Edmond Monroe, granted 21 September 2005 (Box 252, Folder 4)
      - McPhatter, Chesley Franklin, Jr., granted 24 March 2005 (Box 252, Folder 4)
      - McWhirt, Carlene Marie, granted 6 December 2005 (Box 252, Folder 4)
      - Meador, Donald Lee, granted 23 February 2005 (Box 252, Folder 4)
      - Meadows, Tammy Renee Hartman, granted 14 June 2005 (Box 252, Folder 4)
      - Mealy, Vergetta, granted 5 October 2005 (Box 252, Folder 5)
      - Megginson, Amy Dale, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 252, Folder 5)
      - Mendoza, Conrad Ian, granted 25 July 2005 (Box 252, Folder 5)
      - Meredith, Bobby Don, granted 26 May 2005 (Box 252, Folder 5)
      - Merricks, James Kevin, granted 31 August 2005 (Box 252, Folder 5)
      - Merriner, Melanie Ann, granted 1 November 2005 (Box 252, Folder 5)
      - Michael, Joshua Andrew, granted 27 October 2005 (Box 252, Folder 5)
      - Middleton, Randy Keith, granted 10 June 2005 (Box 252, Folder 5)
      - Miles, Matthew David, granted 5 December 2005 (Box 253, Folder 1)
      - Miller, Dallas Winford, granted 25 July 2005 (Box 253, Folder 1)
      - Miller, James A., IV, granted 11 January 2006 (Box 253, Folder 1)
      - Miller, Linwood Lee, Sr., granted 10 June 2005 (Box 253, Folder 2)
      - Mills, Grace M., granted 16 May 2005 (Box 253, Folder 2)
      - Mills, Richard Allen, granted 5 October 2005 (Box 253, Folder 2)
      - Mingo, Mario G., granted 5 July 2005 (Box 253, Folder 2)
      - Minor, Sharon Clementine, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 253, Folder 2)
      - Mitchell, Robert A., granted 25 July 2005 (Box 253, Folder 3)
      - Mizell, Kerry Leon, granted 31 August 2005 (Box 253, Folder 3)
      - Mohr, Julie Ann, granted 19 December 2005 (Box 253, Folder 3)
      - Monson, Brian Keith, granted 19 December 2005 (Box 253, Folder 3)
      - Montgomery, Timothy Shane, granted 22 August 2005 (Box 253, Folder 3)
      - Moore, Dallas Lee, granted 22 November 2005 (Box 253, Folder 3)
      - Moore, Daniel Bruce, granted 27 October 2005 (Box 253, Folder 4)
      - Moore, Douglas Edward, granted 4 January 2006 (Box 253, Folder 4)
      - Moore, Fred Lee, Jr., granted 17 June 2005 (Box 253, Folder 4)
      - Moore, Robert F., Jr., granted 19 August 2005 (Box 253, Folder 4)
      - Moore, Steven Glenn, granted 31 August 2005 (Box 253, Folder 4)
      - Moore, Susan E., granted 22 November 2005 (Box 253, Folder 4)
      - Moore-Whittaker, Marilyn Ann, granted 19 December 2005 (Box 253, Folder 4)
      - Morales, Elaine, granted 24 October 2005 (Box 253, Folder 5)
      - Moretti, Gary Vincent, granted 19 December 2005 (Box 253, Folder 5)
      - Morgan, Sandra Evette, granted 17 June 2005 (Box 253, Folder 5)
      - Morgan-Keeles, Andrea, granted 22 November 2005 (Box 253, Folder 5)
      - Morris, James Arnold, granted 16 August 2005 (Box 253, Folder 5)
      - Morris, Larry Eldon, Sr., granted 14 June 2005 (Box 253, Folder 5)
      - Morris, Robert James, Jr., granted 5 October 2005 (Box 254, Folder 1)
      - Morris, William Kenneth, Sr., granted 21 September 2005 (Box 254, Folder 1)
      - Morris, Wilson G., granted 23 February 2005 (Box 254, Folder 1)
      - Morrison, Anthony, granted 24 October 2005 (Box 254, Folder 1)
      - Morter, Kenneth Edward, granted 23 February 2005 (Box 254, Folder 1)
      - Morton, Edward M., Jr., granted 15 February 2005 (Box 254, Folder 1)
      - Morton, Feleta Coronette, granted 24 March 2005 (Box 254, Folder 2)
      - Moseley, Verlon E., granted 26 September 2005 (Box 254, Folder 2)
      - Moses, Karen Elizabeth, granted 15 February 2005 (Box 254, Folder 2)
      - Mosley, Natalie Vernice, granted 1 June 2005 (Box 254, Folder 2)
      - Moss, Janice Leano, granted 5 October 2005 (Box 254, Folder 2)
      - Moss, John David, granted 6 July 2005 (Box 254, Folder 2)
      - Mostoller, Barbara W., granted 15 February 2005 (Box 254, Folder 2)
      - Mountcastle, Jerry Cooper, granted 17 May 2005 (Box 254, Folder 3)
      - Muhammad, Frank Waheed, granted 14 November 2005 (Box 254, Folder 3)
      - Mullins, Debra Carol, granted 15 February 2005 (Box 254, Folder 3)
      - Munsey, Clinton Mitchell, granted 16 August 2005 (Box 254, Folder 3)
      - Murphy, James Curtis, granted 20 June 2005 (Box 254, Folder 3)
      - Murphy, Ralph Carl, granted 16 November 2005 (Box 254, Folder 3)
      - Murphy-Brown, Lois Ann, granted 5 July 2005 (Box 254, Folder 3)
      - Murray, Barbara Anne, granted 15 February 2005 (Box 254, Folder 4)
      - Musick, Thomas Conrad, granted 5 December 2005 (Box 254, Folder 4)
      - Myers, Brian Christopher, granted 9 September 2005 (Box 254, Folder 4)
      - Myers, Seth, granted 10 June 2005 (Box 254, Folder 4)
      - Myers, Valerie, granted 9 September 2005 (Box 254, Folder 4)
      - Nabizad, Ahmad Y., granted 26 May 2005 (Box 254, Folder 4)
      - Napier, Kimberly Dawn, granted 14 September 2005 (Box 254, Folder 5)
      - Napier, Warren Lewis, granted 24 March 2005 (Box 254, Folder 5)
      - Neel, Stephen Damian, granted 22 November 2005 (Box 254, Folder 5)
      - Neighbors, Mary Rose, granted 21 September 2005 (Box 254, Folder 5)
      - Nelson, Aurealia Novella, granted 18 October 2005 (Box 254, Folder 5)
      - Neugent, Rex Allen, granted 16 November 2005 (Box 255, Folder 1)
      - Nevitt, Dennis Michael, granted 15 February 2005 (Box 255, Folder 1)
      - Newcome, Jeffrey Kirk, granted 9 September 2005 (Box 255, Folder 1)
      - Newman, John Wesley, granted 19 August 2005 (Box 255, Folder 1)
      - Newton, Albert, III, granted 26 May 2005 (Box 255, Folder 1)
      - Newton, Ethel G., granted 19 December 2005 (Box 255, Folder 1)
      - Nichols, Arley Berkley, granted 18 October 2005 (Box 255, Folder 2)
      - Nichols, Mark F., granted 26 May 2005 (Box 255, Folder 2)
      - Nichols, Thomas Hayes, Jr., granted 15 February 2005 (Box 255, Folder 2)
      - Nicholson-YaaGoubi, Valarie Almaleta, granted 14 June 2005 (Box 255, Folder 2)
      - Nimety, Lewis Daniel, granted 18 October 2005 (Box 255, Folder 2)
      - Nix, Clarence, granted 26 May 2005 (Box 255, Folder 3)
      - Norris, Christine M., granted 3 January 2006 (Box 255, Folder 3)
      - Norris, George C., Sr., granted 14 November 2005 (Box 255, Folder 3)
      - Nuckolls, Jeffery L., granted 18 October 2005 (Box 255, Folder 3)
      - Nunnally, Joan Marie, granted 24 March 2005 (Box 255, Folder 3)
      - Nutter, Penny Ann, granted 17 May 2005 (Box 255, Folder 3)
      - Nyberg, Thomas Edward, granted 21 September 2005 (Box 255, Folder 3)
      - Oakes, Shirley, granted 16 November 2005 (Box 255, Folder 4)
      - Oakley, Brian Keith, granted 30 November 2005 (Box 255, Folder 4)
      - Obolewicz, Barbara Ann, granted 16 May 2005 (Box 255, Folder 4)
      - O'Farrow, Rachel Ann Butler, granted 23 February 2005 (Box 255, Folder 4)
      - Ohse, Martha, granted 18 October 2005 (Box 255, Folder 4)
      - Olander, Daniel Fisher, granted 27 October 2005 (Box 255, Folder 5)
      - Olds, Corey A., granted 7 November 2005 (Box 255, Folder 5)
      - O'Quinn, Vernon, granted 5 December 2005 (Box 255, Folder 5)
      - Orange, Linda G., granted 22 November 2005 (Box 255, Folder 5)
      - Osborne, Bennie William, granted 19 August 2005 (Box 255, Folder 5)
      - Owens, Jamie Leo, granted 24 January 2005 (Box 255, Folder 5)
      - Pace, Donald C., Sr., granted 26 August 2005 (Box 256, Folder 1)
      - Paddy, Kevin Leonard, granted 16 May 2005 (Box 256, Folder 1)
      - Painter, Noah Elwood, granted 4 January 2006 (Box 256, Folder 1)
      - Palazzola, Salvatore, III, granted 21 September 2005 (Box 256, Folder 1)
      - Palmer, Donna Dierra, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 256, Folder 1)
      - Paradis, Michael Andrew, granted 2 May 2005 (Box 256, Folder 1)
      - Paris, Randall Alan, granted 24 January 2005 (Box 256, Folder 2)
      - Parker, Tina, granted 5 December 2005 (Box 256, Folder 2)
      - Parlow, Samuel Joseph, granted 1 March 2005 (Box 256, Folder 2)
      - Parris, David Wayne, granted 22 November 2005 (Box 256, Folder 2)
      - Parrish, Gillian Elizabeth, granted 17 May 2005 (Box 256, Folder 2)
      - Parsons, Curtis Lee, granted 14 June 2005 (Box 256, Folder 2)
      - Pass, William Spencer, granted 21 November 2005 (Box 256, Folder 3)
      - Patch, Bernard Joseph, granted 24 January 2005 (Box 256, Folder 3)
      - Patrick, Dayna R., granted 21 November 2005 (Box 256, Folder 3)
      - Patterson, Richard A., granted 5 July 2005 (Box 256, Folder 3)
      - Patterson, Rudolph Levonne, granted 20 June 2005 (Box 256, Folder 4)
      - Patterson, Thomas Roosevelt, granted 6 December 2005 (Box 256, Folder 4)
      - Patterson, Vanessa Denise, granted 17 May 2005 (Box 256, Folder 4)
      - Patton, Jeffery Scott, granted 5 December 2005 (Box 256, Folder 4)
      - Paul, Francis James, granted 24 January 2005 (Box 256, Folder 4)
      - Pauley, Charles Junior, granted 24 March 2005 (Box 256, Folder 4)
      - Paulsen, Noah Webster, granted 26 May 2005 (Box 256, Folder 5)
      - Payne, Clinton Cordell, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 256, Folder 5)
      - Payne, Dana M., granted 31 March 2005 (Box 256, Folder 5)
      - Payne, Erika M., granted 19 December 2005 (Box 256, Folder 5)
      - Payne, Geneva Bertelson, granted 15 November 2005 (Box 256, Folder 5)
      - Payne, James M., granted 15 November 2005 (Box 256, Folder 5)
      - Payne, John Andrew, granted 1 March 2005 (Box 257, Folder 1)
      - Payne, Kenneth Arnold, granted 5 July 2005 (Box 257, Folder 1)
      - Payne, Leonard M., Jr., granted 21 September 2005 (Box 257, Folder 1)
      - Payne, Wallace, granted 19 August 2005 (Box 257, Folder 1)
      - Payne, Wendell T., granted 1 March 2005 (Box 257, Folder 1)
      - Pedigo, William O., Jr., granted 11 May 2005 (Box 257, Folder 1)
      - Peele, Leslie H., granted 5 July 2005 (Box 257, Folder 1)
      - Pemberton, David B., granted 5 July 2005 (Box 257, Folder 2)
      - Penn, Jecktea Evette, granted 26 May 2005 (Box 257, Folder 2)
      - Perdue, Edward Allan, granted 18 October 2005 (Box 257, Folder 2)
      - Perkins, David Franklin, granted 16 August 2005 (Box 257, Folder 2)
      - Perkins, Richard Henry, Jr., granted 9 September 2005 (Box 257, Folder 2)
      - Perkins, Wendy Dawn, granted 19 August 2005 (Box 257, Folder 2)
      - Perlmutter, Gilbert A., granted 4 October 2005 (Box 257, Folder 3)
      - Perry, Herman, II, granted 19 December 2005 (Box 257, Folder 3)
      - Perry, Terry Pickett, granted 20 June 2005 (Box 257, Folder 3)
      - Perry, Thomas E., granted 5 December 2005 (Box 257, Folder 3)
      - Peterkin-Frazier, Sandra Verlena, granted 16 August 2005 (Box 257, Folder 3)
      - Peters, Edward Lee, granted 9 December 2005 (Box 257, Folder 3)
      - Peterson, LaWana' Rene', granted 27 October 2005 (Box 257, Folder 4)
      - Pettaway, Mary Ruth, granted 14 November 2005 (Box 257, Folder 4)
      - Phillips, Teresa L., granted 5 December 2005 (Box 257, Folder 4)
      - Philyaw, Jeffrey W., granted 16 August 2005 (Box 257, Folder 4)
      - Pierce, Patricia LaNeese, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 257, Folder 4)
      - Pitts, Jeff Anthony, granted 4 October 2005 (Box 257, Folder 5)
      - Pizzullo, Kathie A., granted 21 September 2005 (Box 257, Folder 5)
      - Plaster, John Michael, granted 19 December 2005 (Box 257, Folder 5)
      - Plasters, Lawrence Edward, granted 4 October 2005 (Box 257, Folder 5)
      - Poindexter, Ralph L., granted 19 December 2005 (Box 257, Folder 5)
      - Poindexter, Tracie Meadows, granted 1 June 2005 (Box 258, Folder 1)
      - Pollard, Ellis Denton, granted 4 October 2005 (Box 258, Folder 1)
      - Poole, Rocky Douglas, granted 20 June 2005 (Box 258, Folder 1)
      - Pope, Lana Marie, granted 14 November 2005 (Box 258, Folder 1)
      - Pope, Michael Brian, granted 9 December 2005 (Box 258, Folder 1)
      - Porter, Aaron LaVelle, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 258, Folder 1)
      - Powell, Early, granted 19 December 2005 (Box 258, Folder 1)
      - Power, Billy Charles, granted 5 July 2005 (Box 258, Folder 2)
      - Preston, Tony Ray, granted 15 February 2005 (Box 258, Folder 2)
      - Price, Burlie, granted 21 November 2005 (Box 258, Folder 2)
      - Priest, Sylvia Melissa, granted 26 August 2005 (Box 258, Folder 2)
      - Priet, John Trustan, Jr., granted 21 November 2005 (Box 258, Folder 2)
      - Procise, Ricky, granted 9 September 2005 (Box 258, Folder 3)
      - Proctor, Paulette Diane, granted 9 September 2005 (Box 258, Folder 3)
      - Propps, Franklin S., granted 24 January 2005 (Box 258, Folder 3)
      - Puckett, Marlon LaGreg, granted 25 July 2005 (Box 258, Folder 3)
      - Puffinburger, Adam Craig, granted 19 December 2005 (Box 258, Folder 3)
      - Pugh, Mary Augusta, granted 22 August 2005 (Box 258, Folder 3)
      - Pulcrano, Donna, granted 10 June 2005 (Box 258, Folder 3)
      - Queen, Cheryl Lynn, granted 24 March 2005 (Box 258, Folder 4)
      - Quesenberry, Joseph William, granted 27 October 2005 (Box 258, Folder 4)
      - Quintana, Humberto, granted 6 December 2005 (Box 258, Folder 4)
      - Quiroga-Perez, Blanca, granted 26 September 2005 (Box 258, Folder 4)
      - Radford, Michael Ray, granted 16 August 2005 (Box 258, Folder 4)
      - Ragans, Malcolm E., granted 15 February 2005 (Box 258, Folder 4)
      - Rakes, Buford Samuel, granted 26 May 2005 (Box 258, Folder 4)
      - Ramey, Carlene, granted 4 October 2005 (Box 258, Folder 5)
      - Ramos, Eugene Edward, granted 19 December 2005 (Box 258, Folder 5)
      - Ramsey, William David, granted 19 December 2005 (Box 258, Folder 5)
      - Randall, Shirley A., granted 15 February 2005 (Box 258, Folder 5)
      - Randolph, DeWayne Raymond, granted 20 June 2005 (Box 258, Folder 5)
      - Rankins, Anthony M., granted 19 August 2005 (Box 258, Folder 5)
      - Rapacki, Lisa Marie, granted 26 September 2005 (Box 259, Folder 1)
      - Rashad, Hassan Saleem, granted 28 November 2005 (Box 259, Folder 1)
      - Rasnake, Herman, granted 6 December 2005 (Box 259, Folder 1)
      - Raumer, Fredrick Michael, Jr., granted 19 December 2005 (Box 259, Folder 1)
      - Ray, Sarah V., granted 16 August 2005 (Box 259, Folder 1)
      - Reagan, Laura Jane, granted 25 July 2005 (Box 259, Folder 2)
      - Reece, Denise E., granted 6 July 2005 (Box 259, Folder 2)
      - Reed, Raymond David, granted 20 June 2005 (Box 259, Folder 2)
      - Reid, Farnum Thomas, Jr., granted 26 September 2005 (Box 259, Folder 2)
      - Reid, Herbert Lewis, Jr., granted 27 October 2005 (Box 259, Folder 3)
      - Repass, Harry Wayne, granted 21 November 2005 (Box 259, Folder 3)
      - Reynolds, Walter Doafe, granted 24 March 2005 (Box 259, Folder 3)
      - Rice, Robert Alan, granted 16 May 2005 (Box 259, Folder 3)
      - Richardson, Donna Marie, granted 9 September 2005 (Box 259, Folder 3)
      - Richardson, Jarrett Thomas, granted 19 December 2005 (Box 259, Folder 3)
      - Richardson, Tavon Charles, granted 15 February 2005 (Box 259, Folder 4)
      - Riddick, Mildred Perry, granted 19 August 2005 (Box 259, Folder 4)
      - Riddick, Sherry Lynn, granted 15 February 2005 (Box 259, Folder 4)
      - Riggs, Denver Lee, granted 4 October 2005 (Box 259, Folder 4)
      - Rigney, Carl Ray, granted 15 February 2005 (Box 259, Folder 4)
      - Riley, Jeffrey Douglas, granted 1 June 2005 (Box 259, Folder 4)
      - Ring, Jeffrey Kirk, granted 19 December 2005 (Box 259, Folder 5)
      - Ritchey, Stephen Eugene, granted 25 July 2005 (Box 259, Folder 5)
      - Roach, Dennis Ray, granted 14 July 2005 (Box 259, Folder 5)
      - Roberts, Barbara Jean, granted 19 August 2005 (Box 259, Folder 5)
      - Roberts, Jody Clay, granted 16 August 2005 (Box 259, Folder 5)
      - Roberts, Kenyatta D., granted 12 July 2005 (Box 259, Folder 5)
      - Roberts, Virginia L.R., granted 20 June 2005 (Box 260, Folder 1)
      - Robertson, Christopher M., granted 3 January 2006 (Box 260, Folder 1)
      - Robertson, Gary Elroy, granted 14 June 2005 (Box 260, Folder 1)
      - Robertson, James A., granted 20 July 2005 (Box 260, Folder 1)
      - Robertson, Lisa Yvette, granted 19 August 2005 (Box 260, Folder 1)
      - Robinson, Alton L., granted 11 May 2005 (Box 260, Folder 1)
      - Robinson, Brian Lee, granted 7 November 2005 (Box 260, Folder 1)
      - Robinson, Jonquil Lazette, granted 9 September 2005 (Box 260, Folder 2)
      - Robinson, Lenair Darren, granted 19 August 2005 (Box 260, Folder 2)
      - Robinson, Rodney Carl, granted 6 December 2005 (Box 260, Folder 2)
      - Robinson, Sharon Elaine, granted 16 August 2005 (Box 260, Folder 2)
      - Robinson, Tonisha Raylene, granted 6 December 2005 (Box 260, Folder 2)
      - Roche, Kenneth Edward, granted 15 November 2005 (Box 260, Folder 3)
      - Rodriquez, Susan Marie, granted 27 October 2005 (Box 260, Folder 3)
      - Rogers, William Larry, granted 16 August 2005 (Box 260, Folder 3)
      - Rogosky, Mark Kazys, granted 5 July 2005 (Box 260, Folder 3)
      - Rojas, Ezequiel, granted 16 August 2005 (Box 260, Folder 3)
      - Roller, Kenneth Blair, granted 12 July 2005 (Box 260, Folder 3)
      - Roltsch, Mark Harold, granted 21 November 2005 (Box 260, Folder 4)
      - Roomian, Jacquelyn Shell, granted 31 August 2005 (Box 260, Folder 4)
      - Root, Linda G. Campbell, granted 16 August 2005 (Box 260, Folder 4)
      - Roots, Renard Brandon, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 260, Folder 4)
      - Rorie, Michael S., granted 4 October 2005 (Box 260, Folder 4)
      - Rorrer, John Merryman, granted 26 September 2005 (Box 260, Folder 4)
      - Rose, David Eli, Sr., granted 18 October 2005 (Box 260, Folder 5)
      - Rose, Ellen Marie, granted 4 January 2006 (Box 260, Folder 5)
      - Rose, Malcolm Eugene, granted 5 July 2005 (Box 260, Folder 5)
      - Rose, Wendy Paige, granted 16 August 2005 (Box 260, Folder 5)
      - Rosen, Lawrence L., granted 15 February 2005 (Box 260, Folder 5)
      - Ross, Russell M., granted 16 May 2005 (Box 261, Folder 1)
      - Ross, Torris Monell, granted 27 October 2005 (Box 261, Folder 1)
      - Rosson, Jeffrey Wayne, granted 4 January 2006 (Box 261, Folder 1)
      - Rowland, Phill James, granted 19 August 2005 (Box 261, Folder 1)
      - Rowzie, Karla A., granted 11 May 2005 (Box 261, Folder 1)
      - Rucker, Marc Anthony Lee, granted 6 December 2005 (Box 261, Folder 1)
      - Rudolph, Connie Lane, granted 19 August 2005 (Box 261, Folder 2)
      - Ruffin, James M., granted 16 May 2005 (Box 261, Folder 2)
      - Runner, Robert Lee, granted 16 November 2005 (Box 261, Folder 2)
      - Rutherford, Nancy Carol, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 261, Folder 2)
      - Rutherford, Timothy, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 261, Folder 2)
      - Sage, Pamalee, granted 14 November 2005 (Box 261, Folder 2)
      - Saldierna, Georgia Packett, granted 16 August 2005 (Box 261, Folder 3)
      - Salemi, Sheri Tyree, granted 5 July 2005 (Box 261, Folder 3)
      - Salley, John Michael, granted 26 May 2005 (Box 261, Folder 3)
      - Sampson, Carolyn Denise, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 261, Folder 3)
      - Sandidge, Barbara Ellen Hill, granted 19 August 2005 (Box 261, Folder 3)
      - Sandidge, James Robert, granted 19 August 2005 (Box 261, Folder 3)
      - Saunders, Kenneth Eugene, granted 12 July 2005 (Box 261, Folder 4)
      - Saunders, Tracie Lee, granted 24 March 2005 (Box 261, Folder 4)
      - Savage, George J., Jr., granted 17 June 2005 (Box 261, Folder 4)
      - Sawyer, Dorothy P. Jordan, granted 1 July 2005 (Box 261, Folder 4)
      - Scarbor, Earlene H., granted 12 July 2005 (Box 261, Folder 5)
      - Scearce, Bobby Ray, granted 19 December 2005 (Box 261, Folder 5)
      - Schaidt, Eric Von, granted 7 November 2005 (Box 261, Folder 5)
      - Schrieberg, Stephen Harold, granted 4 November 2005 (Box 261, Folder 5)
      - Schuller, David Allen, granted 3 January 2006 (Box 262, Folder 1)
      - Schwartz, David Eugene, granted 26 May 2005 (Box 262, Folder 1)
      - Scott, Alice Penix, granted 3 January 2006 (Box 262, Folder 1)
      - Scott, Cynthia H., granted 1 July 2005 (Box 262, Folder 1)
      - Scott, Francis M., granted 28 November 2005 (Box 262, Folder 1)
      - Scott, Joseph Hamilton, granted 2 May 2005 (Box 262, Folder 1)
      - Scott, Terrence Lee, granted 19 December 2005 (Box 262, Folder 2)
      - Scott-Johnson, Doris M., granted 31 August 2005 (Box 262, Folder 2)
      - Scrogham, Clay Franklin, granted 6 July 2005 (Box 262, Folder 2)
      - Scruggs, Roger Lee, Jr., granted 24 January 2005 (Box 262, Folder 2)
      - Seccia, Thomas Gaetano, Jr., granted 1 August 2005 (Box 262, Folder 2)
      - Sera, Kristine E., granted 5 July 2005 (Box 262, Folder 2)
      - Setchel, Myron William, Jr., granted 16 August 2005 (Box 262, Folder 3)
      - Sexton, Henry Clay, V, granted 27 October 2005 (Box 262, Folder 3)
      - Sexton, Misty Dawn, granted 19 December 2005 (Box 262, Folder 3)
      - Shaw, Lorenda Ninette, granted 4 October 2005 (Box 262, Folder 3)
      - Shelton, Alvin DeWayne, granted 5 October 2005 (Box 262, Folder 3)
      - Shelton, Garfield Paul, Jr., granted 26 May 2005 (Box 262, Folder 3)
      - Shelton, Michael Frank, granted 4 January 2006 (Box 262, Folder 4)
      - Shifflett, Bruce Wesley, granted 5 July 2005 (Box 262, Folder 4)
      - Shifflett, Vernon Leroy, granted 6 July 2005 (Box 262, Folder 4)
      - Shifflette, Gary Wayne, granted 26 September 2005 (Box 262, Folder 4)
      - Shively, Gary W., granted 4 January 2006 (Box 262, Folder 4)
      - Shoaf, William Laughlin, Jr., granted 26 May 2005 (Box 262, Folder 5)
      - Shogren, Ronald Joseph, granted 16 May 2005 (Box 262, Folder 5)
      - Shortt, Timothy Eugene, granted 19 August 2005 (Box 262, Folder 5)
      - Showers, Ellen J. Curry, granted 4 January 2006 (Box 262, Folder 5)
      - Shugarman, Charles D., granted 26 May 2005 (Box 262, Folder 5)
      - Shupe, Terry L., granted 9 September 2005 (Box 262, Folder 5)
      - Sieg, Mark Robert, granted 16 November 2005 (Box 262, Folder 5)
      - Sikand, Ravindar K., granted 26 May 2005 (Box 263, Folder 1)